Okay now let's go ahead and do a quick hands-on on the Amazon bedrock intelligent prompt routing.
So I'm on the AWS console on Amazon bedrock service. So let me just go ahead and scroll down
and go to this tune. Here you can see prompt router models. So I'll just click on this prompt
router model and it takes me to this page route request between foundation models from the
same family, optimizing for response, quality and cost. So what I can do is I can just click on this
configure prompt router. So I just click on this and I'll just give it a name. So let me just
give it a name. So let me just say demo and then you can give it a description if you like. Now we
have the router settings. So models for routing. So we have to choose two base models. So I'll just
click on select model. Let's select from Amazon so I'll select Amazon Nova Pro. I'll do a apply
then select the second model, Nova Light, apply. Okay now we have to select the fallback model.
Choose the default model for request. They do not meet the routing criteria. The response
quality difference is measured based on the fallback model. So this is going to be our default model.
So for any reason if the request do not meet the routing criteria then it's going to send it to
this fallback model. So in our case let's select the fallback model as Nova Pro and then you have
to define the routing criteria. So define the threshold to use for routing requests between
models. The quality of the difference between the fallback model and the other model response for
each prompt as predicted by the model. Lower values indicate similar responses from other models
to the fallback model. So in our case the fallback model is going to be Nova Pro
and the other model is going to be the Nova Light. So I can define the quality threshold. So let's
say 10%. Now if our prompt router determines the quality of the difference is less than 10% then it's
going to route the request to Nova Light. Otherwise it's going to send it to Nova Pro. And if there is
any model that does not meet the criteria then it's still going to go to the fallback model which is
Nova Pro. So you can also put the tags if you want but I'm going to ignore that let me just click on
submit. Okay now you can see it has configured this prompt router. So let me just click on this demo
and if I see the details you can see the details here. So you have the Nova Pro, you have the
ARN for Nova Pro then you have the Amazon resource name or the ARN for Nova Light. And then we know
our fallback model is again Nova Pro. So it's the same one what we have here. But the most important
thing here is this particular Amazon resource name or the ARN which is for the prompt router. So in
case we are using this programmatically what we can do is we can provide this ARN and then behind
the scenes the prompt router is going to determine whether it wants to send the request to this
particular model or the Nova Light. Okay so that's how you can optimize your JNIA application
using this prompt router for your cost latency and accuracy. Okay so that's pretty much it
from this lecture I'll see in the next lecture. Thank you.